The last video, we motivated the idea of replacing
在上个视频中 我们逐步讲解了
a fully connected layer with a locally connected layer.
将完全连接层替换为局部连接层这一概念
This locally connected layer contained fewer weights,
这种局部连接层包含更少的权重
which were shared across space.
并在空间内共享
In this video, we formalized that intuition and defined
在此视频中我们通过图形的形式阐述了这一概念
convolutional layers which are one type of
并定义了卷积层
hidden layer that you will encounter in a convolutional neural network.
它是一种隐藏层 你在卷积神经网络中将会遇到
First, we break the image up into smaller pieces.
首先 我们将图片拆分为更小的部分
In the last video,
在上个视频中
we broke our image into four equally sized pieces,
我们将图片分成了四个相同大小的区域
color coded red, green, yellow, and blue.
标为红色 绿色 黄色和蓝色
Towards breaking up the image for building a convolutional layer,
在拆分图片以构建卷积层的过程中
we first select a width and height that defines a convolution window.
我们首先选择定义卷积窗的宽度和高度
We then simply slide this window
然后在图片像素矩阵上
horizontally and vertically over the matrix of image pixels.
水平和垂直地滑动该卷积窗
At each position, the window specifies a small piece within the image
在每个位置 卷积窗都在图片中指定一个小部分
and defines a collection of pixels to which we connect a single hidden node.
并定义一组连接到单个隐藏节点的像素
We call this hidden layer a convolutional layer.
我们将此隐藏层称为卷积层
But let's dig a little deeper into how a regional collection of
我们深入了解下区域性输入节点集合
input nodes influences the value of a node in the convolutional layer.
对卷积层中的节点的值有何影响
We could represent the weights connecting the nodes
我们可以通过在箭头上方写上值
by writing a numerical value on top of the arrows.
表示连接这些节点的权重
Then in order to get the value of a node in the convolutional layer for this image input,
然后 为了获取该图片输入的卷积层中节点的值
we operate as we did with neural networks with multiplying
我们就像处理神经网络一样操作
the input nodes by their corresponding weights and summing up the result.
我们将输入节点与对应的权重相乘 然后对结果求和
When we do that, we get zero.
求和后的结果是 0
Just as with neural networks there is a bias.
和神经网络一样 存在偏差
For now, assume that the bias is zero.
暂时假设该偏差是 0
We'll always add a ReLu activation function to our convolutional layers.
我们始终会向卷积层添加一个 ReLu 激活函数
Recall the ReLu function leaves
ReLu 激活函数使正值保持不变
positive values alone and sends all negative values to zero.
并将所有负值变成 0
In this case, our zero stays zero.
这里 0 保持不变
And thus, we can plug in the value for the first node in the convolutional layer.
因此 我们可以代入卷积层第一个节点的值
The values of all other nodes are calculated in exactly the same way.
然后按照完全相同的方式计算所有其他节点的值
With first multiplying each input node by the weights.
首先将每个输入节点与权重相乘
Now, we get a negative two.
这个节点的值是 -2
Recall the bias is still zero,
偏差依然是 0
so we won't add anything.
所以不用加上任何值
But now, when we apply the ReLu activation function,
但是现在应用 ReLu 激活函数的话
our negative two is transformed to zero.
-2 变成了 0
We can repeat this process to get the value
我们可以重复这一流程
of every other node in the convolutional layer.
算出卷积层所有其他节点的值
We'll see that instead of representing the weights on top of the arrows,
我们会发现将权重放在网格里
it will prove more convenient to represent them in a grid.
比写在箭头上方更方便
When the weights are represented in a grid in this way,
以这种方式将权重放入网格中后
we call the grid a filter.
我们将该网格称为过滤器
Its size will always match the size of the convolutional window.
它的大小始终与卷积窗的大小一样
In this case, our filter has a height of three and a width of three.
这里 我们的过滤器宽和高都为 3
Now the process of calculating the values of
现在计算隐藏层中节点的值这一流程
the nodes in the hidden layer is much more intuitive.
更直观了
Let's see how it looks when we calculate
我们看看计算卷积层中
the value of the first node in the convolutional layer.
第一个节点的值效果如何
Again, we start with multiplying each of
同样 我们首先将每个输入节点
the input nodes with their corresponding weights and summing up the result.
与对应的权重相乘 然后对结果求和
This yielded zero, and so applying the ReLu activation function again yields zero.
求和之后是 0 因此应用 ReLu 激活函数后还是 0
But what's happening with these large values of three?
但是对于这个大的值 3 会怎样？
Let's inspect the corresponding section of the image.
我们看看相应的图片部分
You'll notice that the positive values in the filter
你会发现过滤器中的正值
perfectly correspond to the largest values in this region of the image.
正好对应的是这个图片区域最大的值
The converse is also true.
反之亦然
The negative values in the filter corresponding to the smallest values in the image.
过滤器中的负值对应的是图片中最小的值
In fact, since we rescaled the pixels in the image to lie between zero and one,
实际上 因为我们对图片中的像素进行了调整 使其位于 0 到 1 之间
with one representing white and zero representing a black pixel.
1 表示白色 0 表示黑色
This three is the largest value that we can
这个 3 是我们可以从此过滤器的卷积层中
get in the convolutional layer for this filter.
获得的最大值
That is the pattern in this region with a diagonal white stripe down the middle,
这就是该区域的规律 对角线白色长条
is the only arrangement of pixels that will yield this maximal value.
是唯一可以产生这个最大值的像素分布
We see that the three is also repeated here and can
我们看到这里也出现了 3
verify that the corresponding region in the image is identical.
并且可以验证图片的相应区域是一样的
But looking back at the filter,
但是再看看过滤器
where we've also depicted larger numbers with lighter colors.
我们用浅色表示更大的数字
You can see that the patterns match,
可以看出规律是相符的
each depicts a light diagonal stripe.
每个都描绘了一个浅色斜条纹
In fact, when we use convolutional neural networks will often visualize the filters,
实际上 当我们使用卷积神经网络时  我们经常会可视化过滤器
and that visualization will tell us
该可视化图表会告诉我们
what kind of pattern the filter is designed to detect.
过滤器会检测到什么样的规律
Just like in neural networks,
就像在神经网络中一样
these weights will not be set in advance and will instead be
我们不会提前设置这些权重
learned by the network as the weights that minimize our loss function.
而是由网络去判断哪些权重可以最小化损失函数
So far, our network only has one filter and so we're only
到目前为止 我们的网络只有一个过滤器
able to gain information as to whether a single pattern was detected or not.
因此我们只能获得是否检测到了一个规律的信息
If we wanted to discover more patterns,
如果我们想检测更多规律
we would need to use more filters.
则需要使用更多过滤器
In the next video,
在下个视频中
we'll continue our discussion of convolutional layers and begin by discussing,
我们将继续讲解卷积层
why you would want to search for more than just a single pattern in an image?
并讲解为何要在图片中寻找更多规律？